kdramastars.com 2019-04-07

# KDramaStars

#### PRIVACY POLICY

Welcome to KDramaStars's privacy policy. We have developed this policy as part of our commitment to protecting your privacy, while providing a valuable and personalized service. We want you to feel confident about the privacy and security of your personal information. This policy applies whether or not you register any details for KDramaStars services.

We may collect personal information about you when you register with KDramaStars.

When KDramaStars asks you for details about yourself this is because we want to ensure that we give you a service that's tailored for you. We ask for as little information as possible in order to make it a quick and easy process. The information you give us isn't sold on to other companies and we have a serious and dedicated commitment to the security of your information.

#### WHAT INFORMATION MIGHT I HAVE TO GIVE AS A USER OF KDRAMASTARS?

If you register for services, we ask you for a small amount of information. We do this so that we can give you a service that's tailored for you, and so that we may serve you better. We only collect the minimum information required to identify you and to ensure that we provide you with appropriate information. Details we collect may include:

first name and last name;  
company name;  
address;  
telephone number;  
e-mail address.

#### IS MY INFORMATION SECURE?

Yes. We take the security of your personal data extremely seriously. We have implemented technology and security policies designed to protect the personal data under our control. We also follow strict security procedures as required by the US Data Protection Act 1998. These cover the storage and disclosure of any information you've provided, and the prevention of unauthorized access.

#### CAN ANYBODY ELSE WHO'S USING KDRAMASTARS ACCESS MY PERSONAL DETAILS?

No. All personal information given to KDramaStars is secured and stored away from public access.

#### CAN I CORRECT OR CHANGE ANY DETAILS I'VE GIVEN TO YOU?

Yes. You can make changes to any of the information you gave us when you registered.

#### THIRD PARTY LINKS

KDramaStars contains links to other sites. We cannot assume responsibility for any other site's content or information handling practices. We encourage you to review each site's privacy policy before entering into transactions with them.

If you would like more information about the information collection practices of a particular third-party advertising service provider, or if you would like more information on how to opt out of a third-party advertising service provider’s information collection practices, go to [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/), or for apps, at <http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices>.  
Additionally, some of our third-party advertising service providers are members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI"). You can obtain more information about these third-party advertising service providers' information collection practices, and opt out of such practices (and at the same time opt out of the collection practices of other, or all, NAI members) by following the opt out instructions on the NAI's website at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.  
Please note that one of our third-party advertising service providers is DoubleClick. You can opt out of the use of cookies by DoubleClick by visiting <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>.

#### Contact us:

E-mail : info at kdramastars.com
